careercrate.com 2017-06-03

# CareerCrate | Privacy Policy

**The Privacy Policy Page**

Privacy Statement Information

Because CareerCrate gathers information about the viewers of www.CareerCrate.com, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information.

Information CareerCrate gathers and tracks

CareerCrate gathers two types of information about users: 1) Data that users provide through optional, voluntary registration on our site, and 2) aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. Such information enables us to better tailor our content to viewers' needs and help our advertisers better understand the demographics of our audience. Because CareerCrate derives a portion of its revenue from advertising, providing such aggregated demographic data is essential in order to keep some of our services free to users.

CareerCrate is committed to protecting your privacy. CareerCrate does not provide this information to any third parties. However, by using this website you acknowledge and agree that CareerCrate may, in its sole discretion, preserve or disclose your Content, as well as your information, such as email addresses, IP addresses, timestamps, and other user information, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: comply with legal process; enforce these Terms of Use; respond to claims that any Content violates the rights of third-parties; respond to claims that contact information (for example phone number, street address) of a third-party has been posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; protect the rights, property, or personal safety of CareerCrate, its users or the general public.

Electronic Newsletters

CareerCrate may offer free electronic newsletters to users. CareerCrate gathers the e-mail addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Customers may remove themselves from any mailing list by following the instructions contained in every newsletter.

Surveys

CareerCrate occasionally conducts customer surveys to better target our content and product inventory to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our advertisers and partners. We never share any information about specific individuals with any third party, except as noted previously.

Usage tracking

CareerCrate tracks user traffic patterns throughout CareerCrate and this information is correlated with data about individual users. Overall usage statistics, according to a user's domain name, browser type and MIME type gotten by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser), are also broken down.

CareerCrate also tracks and catalogs the search terms that customers enter into our search tools, but this tracking is never associated with individual users.

Use of the information

CareerCrate uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites,whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users. 

As stated above, CareerCrate may use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and enable users to participate in polls and message boards. CareerCrate never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers or partners.

We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. CareerCrate does not track what individual users view, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

We track search terms entered in our search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don't track which terms a particular user enters.

CareerCrate creates aggregrate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. CareerCrate never shares individual personal information with anyone, so an advertiser will never know that a specific user clicked their ad.

CareerCrate uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience demographics. We do not share information about individual users with any third party, with the exceptions noted previously.

Third Party Target Advertising Companies

CareerCrate uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to our Website and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.On this Website, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to this Website's users based on their visit to this Website and other websites on the Internet. For more information on the DART cookie see:�http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by Google by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy at:�http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. Users may opt out of targeting advertising for all NAI member ad networks by visiting:�http://www.networkadvertising.org/.

By publishing an ad in CareerCrate, the user understand and agrees that the ads and content are public and accesible by any third party and that they may appear in results of search engines (such as Yahoo!, MSN, Google, Altavista, and other search engines) and in the cache of those search engines, in feeds and other web sites by cobranding agreements and that it is the sole responsability of each of those search engines, web sites or RSS web feed resources to maintain updated their indexes and their cache and to remove content or ads from their indexes and their cache being impossible for CareerCrate to influence or correct such ads or contents.CareerCrate shall not be liable for the information published in the result of the searchs or by any other web site that have include in their servers the ads or contents of the user of CareerCrate.

Opt-Out Policy

CareerCrate gives users options wherever necessary and practical, such choices include: 

Opting not to receive our electronic newsletters when registering for a site

Opting not to provide certain personal information when registering for a site or service

Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need for any information from our users

Unsubscribe Policy

Users may unsubscribe to any of our electronic newsletters at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of each newsletter.

How To Contact Us

Contact Us:

Administration:admin@careercrate.com

Support :support@careercrate.com

Address:

216 Gilmour ave, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, M6P 3B4

Tel:+1 416 788 0144

.
